Where you goin'?
DOA's name is Caleb Easton.
Jay Easton's son.
Yeah. his dad's a billionaire.
Why am I being told
a Brooklyn homicide detective
wants your advice on an overdose death?
I don't care what you did at the NYPD.
You're the ex-cop.
I heard you requested my squad.
I just need information
about Adrian Murado.
You suspected him of trafficking girls.
The details of his death are similar to
the recent homicide of Caleb Easton.
Both victims have a girlfriend
who no one had met
and both times
the girlfriend disappeared.
Can't be the same woman.
Why would she kill an ex-con
and then a year later.
do the same thing to Jay Easton's son?
How are those two guys connected?
I'm Jinny. Is there any way
you could help me get an ID?
Who's Oliver Charles?
Fancy rich lawyer guy trying to bag.
You saw a woman
walk into your neighbor's house
in the middle of the night?
Well. I didn't really see her face.
She did have a tattoo. though.
A little red flower.
I looked you up.
You were in this hospital a year ago.
Your cop boyfriend
knock you around a little?
Victims of violence are the most violent.
Don't you think so?
Really made a mess last night.
Fuck. It was so fun.
Wish we could just stay here
all day and do this.
- We can't?
- I'm slammed this week.
But. you know. maybe we can
hang out again sometime soon.
Let me walk you down.
I'll get you an Uber.
Do I take this with me?
Uh. yeah. that's your copy.
and I have a copy.
But. uh. listen.
I. uh. I really enjoyed this.
A lot.
It says I can't say anything about you.
I can't do anything to hurt you
or you'll destroy me.
It's like you own me.
No. it's just. you know. it says
that you can't share any information.
and there's a liability clause. but...
I want you to own me.
I wanna belong to you.
Look.
I'm just a lawyer. okay?
And I know we did
a lot of drugs last night.
But I'm not really into the crazy stuff.
What if I just. like...
stayed here all day...
and waited for you to come home?
I... I'm not... I can't.
You have cameras.
You can watch.
Make sure I don't do anything wrong.
I'm not... I'm not gonna give you
a key to my apartment.
I don't want a key.
I want to be locked up.
Jesus.
Look. I... I gotta go. okay?
But...
Hey. you know. I want you naked.
And cleaning.
Clean my whole fucking apartment.
When Caleb Easton was murdered.
he was seeing a woman
with a poppy tattoo on her stomach.
Now. look at the girl in the bodega video
with Adrian Murado.
She has the same tattoo.
It's the same girl.
- It's something.
- I know.
- But it's not enough.
- Yeah.
It's a tattoo.
People have the same tattoos.
That's not enough to prove
it's the same woman. and you know that.
Are you whispering? What's happening?
Yeah.
Same reason you're talking to me
from your car.
My lieutenant doesn't want me doing this.
Jay Easton has hospitals
with his name on them.
He throws all kinds of money
at all the police pension funds.
We can't link his son
to fucking Adrian Murado.
a suspected sex trafficker.
based on one tattoo?
No one's gonna take us seriously
unless we can find
more of a connection
between these two guys.
I did a deep dive on Easton.
I got nothing.
Caleb Easton's clean.
Oh. wait.
He reported a stolen vehicle once.
Did you send that to me? Send that to me.
In other news. Amy invited me
to a thing this weekend. Are you going?
What?
Are you going
to your sister's engagement party?
So. we'll find a connection between
Caleb Easton and Adrian Murado.
Can I talk to Caleb's family?
Are you going
to your sister's engagement party?
Can I talk to Caleb's family?
I'm not doing this right now.
I'll talk to you fucking later.
Yeah. you played this well.
Uh. what?
Nora Washington. the head of C20.
requested to read an assessment
of the Caleb Easton homicide.
So. I've been overruled.
You went behind my back. and it worked.
- I didn't go...
- Write it up.
Get it done.
Oliver's one of our partners.
Hey. hi.
Hello. It's lovely to meet you.
He does a lot of pro bono work
supporting girls' education
all over the world.
You know. it's so important to me.
especially as the father of a daughter.
- to raise up the next generation.
- Yes.
Girls' education is just...
one of the best ways we have
to protect our future.
It strengthens the economy.
It builds strong communities.
Give me one second.
I need these to read my email now.
I'm getting old.
Uh...
Okay.
Jinny?
Where are you?
Hey. Jinny.
Fuck.
I've been waiting for you.
Lie down.
And don't move.
I want to look at you.
Stop looking at me like that.
W-Where are you going?
Hey. Jinny.
I'm coming in there to get you.
No!
Come on.
Jinny.
It was different when I was a cop.
We didn't have this much paperwork.
We didn't have time.
We were just trying to clear cases.
I. I didn't have a lot of mentors.
But here. I can't even call it a case
until I prove it's a case.
This isn't a case yet.
I know. It's an assessment of a case...
You need more background. Details.
The only connection
between the two homicides
is a girl in a video from 2012.
And you haven't even
interviewed the officer
who made the report at the bodega?
- I read the report.
- Why haven't you spoken to him?
His name is Tim Baker.
Yeah. and the detective
I'm working with knows him.
You're an FBI agent. come on.
Tim.
I only got a few minutes.
I gotta be in court.
Hi. Alice Black. I'm a special agent.
but I actually used to work
with Danny Kelly in homicide.
Skinny little Danny?
- Yeah.
- I still can't believe he made detective.
- Oh. Me neither.
- Listen. uh. I'd love to help.
but this report was. what. 14 years ago?
I. I. I got called in by the owner
of the bodega.
It was a disturbance.
It was a male and a female.
A teenager.
And the man said he was her dad.
He told me he'd been looking for her.
She was high and she needed a place
to sleep it off.
And the girl told me
she wanted to stay with her dad.
We talked about this at the time. Nora.
I mean. I didn't know
you were looking into this guy.
I didn't have any reason to think
that he was bullshitting me.
What was across the street
from the bodega. Tim?
- Nora.
- The bodega was across from a tug joint
called the Candlelight Lounge.
where the cops like to go
to blow off steam.
- Right?
- You think none of your fed buddies
ever went there to get jerked off?
Candlelight Lounge.
isn't that a stupid name?
You don't think they could have been
a little more creative?
- You know. I'm here as a favor.
- Candlelight Club.
- You got the alliteration.
- You're treating me
like a fucking skel. I'm done.
- Happy House.
- Tim. did you ever verify
that he was her dad?
Everything I know is in the report.
And it was 14 years ago.
You told me you didn't remember
investigating Adrian Murado.
I wasn't investigating him.
I was trying to shut down
the fucking massage parlors.
But "laws are spiderwebs
through which the big flies pass
and the little ones get caught."
W-What does that mean?
I think Balzac was saying
cops need handjobs too.
- Law enforcement is a stressful job.
- Why don't you trust me?
Because I don't know
if you're still a cop.
- Of course I'm not.
- You all grew up in the cop neighborhoods
and you went to the same cop schools.
and you watch out for each other.
But you left.
That's what I can't figure out.
Who are you?
Is that him?
Yeah.
This is what happens
every time I leave the house.
I know it's hard. but you just...
you have to make a clean break from him.
It's better for you in the end.
Where do I go? You gave up my bed.
I know. we had to.
But if you wanna come back...
He's gonna kill me. okay? Help me.
You have to help me.
Hey. Becky.
Um...
This is hard to say. but I. um...
The physical part of our friendship.
it... it needs to stop.
It was totally...
lovely.
I think you're a lovely girl.
Um. but it. like. yeah. I could...
I could. like. seriously lose my job.
Not only here. but like...
And it's my... and. you know.
I overstepped.
And we both. you know. contributed to it.
but I... I do want to take responsibility.
and therefore request that we...
reestablish. um. just healthy boundaries
around here.
Okay?
I'm gonna need you to go get the drugs
that you confiscated from me
and give them back right now.
So. no.
I... I cannot do that.
I...
No.
Uh... but...
we can get you help here.
We can do this together.
Hm.
You know. when we had sex...
I took a picture of you.
Why would you do that?
I'm gonna need some latex gloves.
some paper towels.
some surface cleaner with bleach.
and sani-wipes.
Sani-wipes?
You can get them from the supply closet.
It'll be pretty easy.
Hey.
We can do this together.
Where have you been?
I had to meet a friend.
And then I wanted to get some food
to cook for you.
There's something
I want to talk to you about.
Is Jinny Allen your real name?
I had somebody at the firm look you up.
Why?
'Cause I feel like I've met you before.
Is Jinny your real name?
No.
So. what is your real name?
I'm serious.
The fuck is this?
Goddammit. what are you doing?
Ah. shit!
I'm bleeding!
We. uh...
We actually have met before. at a party.
You paid to have sex with me. I was 15.
Um... oh.
Here's a band-aid.
It's a little bit open.
You think it's clean?
Oh. my God.
Please...
It's okay.
- Oh...
- It'll feel good.
I'm not actually from Ohio.
Fuck it.
Sorry.
- Al.
- Hey.
- I came.
- Marshall's here.
Hey.
You coming back upstairs. Danny?
Um...
Al. Hey. I didn't know
he was gonna be here.
No?
Fuck.
There was a raid at the Candlelight Lounge
by the NYPD in 2012.
Three names are listed as
confidential informants with plea deals.
One of them could be Caleb Easton.
It could be a connection to Adrian Murado.
Can you tell me who they were?
- It was your case.
- It never became a case.
As soon as I started poking around.
the police shut the place down.
If you want those names.
you talk to a judge.
I need someone
more senior to vouch for me.
And you're asking me?
You don't trust me. Okay.
What else do you wanna know?
I dated a detective.
He put me in the hospital.
And when I told my lieutenant.
everyone I worked with and grew up with...
stopped talking to me.
So...
I'm not a cop anymore.
I saw the pictures of the raid.
The girls' beds.
They weren't allowed to bathe.
They weren't eating every day.
And not one of the men
buying sex from them.
not one of 'em served time.
No.
The buyers were sent to classes
to learn about human trafficking.
Like they didn't already fucking know.
But you got that place closed.
And if Caleb Easton is one of those CIs...
then we have a case.
Let me make some calls.
Take some donuts and get out of here.
Becky. you can't call me here.
I'm really sorry.
I'm... I'm. like. freaking out.
I should not have given you back
the drugs. and...
He's gonna kill me
if he sees me on the phone.
I just need you to get
a couple more things for me.
No. I can't get you a wig.
I don't know where people get wigs.
I... I went to. like. a hair salon.
and they kind of. like. laughed at me.
But I thought. 'cause...
I'm making chicken. You hungry?
Ah!
Is my dad here?
I'm not going in there
if you're not talking to me.
The whole way out to Connecticut.
you just looked out the fuckin' window.
and it's giving me a stomachache.
I was looking at the beautiful
New England scenery.
Look. I wasn't hanging out with Marshall.
- Can we go in?
- I didn't know he was coming to the bar.
Look. he's a cop. I'm a cop.
I can't control when I see him. okay?
- Okay.
I guess everything's okay then.
Hey. no. wait. Um...
You smell bad.
What?
I was trying to think
of another way to say it.
but now that we're going in there.
when was the last time you took a shower?
What the fuck?
Here. put this on.
- No. No. I smell fine.
- You smell gross.
And I'm not going in there
unless you put this on.
I...
Here. Put it all over your neck.
What is this?
It's orange honey blossom.
It's organic.
Oh. damn it. Danny.
My hands smell like a flower
took a shit on 'em.
Yeah. well.
Did Caleb suffer?
We're still trying to put together
as much information
about what happened as we can.
I know we spoke right after it happened.
but we'd just love to hear more
about your brother's last few months.
Oh.
I don't know much more
than I told you on the phone.
He was. um...
I don't know.
I... I didn't know he was using drugs.
I think he was depressed.
That's so hard.
My dad had some issues with depression.
It can be really tough on a family.
We... we would just go
for months without talking.
Um. but h-he had reached out
to let us know that he had met someone.
He was happy.
I could hear it in his voice.
It's okay.
Did you ask if you could meet her?
Meet her? No.
He said she'd just gotten out
of an abusive...
relationship. I think?
Bad... a bad relationship.
Mm.
Did your brother ever mention
giving her money?
Oh. God. Did he give her money?
No. N-Not that we... not that we've seen.
Can you think of any reason
she'd be targeting him?
No.
Oh.
Any idea why he left the bench in 2012?
Excuse me.
I need to steal my daughter away
to take me to the doctor.
I'm so sorry. My dad isn't well.
I am so grateful for...
everything you are doing
to find out what happened to my son.
- Of course. Mr. Easton.
- Yeah. Absolutely.
We really need to get
a full picture of his life.
We can talk at another time.
We'll contact you.
- He did suffer.
- Al.
What?
When he died...
- he had no food or water in his body.
- Al.
So it's possible she held him for days.
injecting him with drugs
before his body just gave up.
So...
is there any reason why someone
would have wanted to hurt him?
Do you know if your brother
ever went to a massage parlor
called the Candlelight Lounge?
Do you know if he was ever arrested
for solicitation of an underage girl?
We are not going to continue
this conversation at this time.
You can speak to our family lawyer.
Understood.
- Al.
- Please leave.
You...
smell terrible.
You backed down.
- You brought up teenage prostitutes.
- You should have pushed.
You think that's a good way
to get people to talk?
That's not what I do. You know that.
I walk. I don't run.
I listen.
People talk when they think you'll listen.
And what the fuck
is the Candlelight Lounge?
Huh? That's a shitty name.
It was a massage parlor across the street
from the bodega
where Murado was with the girl.
The cops liked to go there.
- You didn't.
- What are you asking?
Have I ever gotten a handjob
from a teenager?
No. Not even when I was a teenager.
You know. is this...
Is this why Tim Baker told me to fuck off?
Is that your plan?
You gonna go around accusing cops?
Tim Baker's a good guy. okay?
And I can't piss him off. okay?
He's high up.
My family situation right now.
I can't piss anyone else off.
That's your party tie?
Yeah. We're going to Amy's.
- I'm not going to that.
- You're going to Amy's.
- I have work to do.
- Your sister's engagement party?
- You're going!
- I don't even know why she invited you.
- She invited me because she knew...
- You're not friends.
- I'd make you go.
- Everyone who meets you
- thinks you're their friend.
- No. I'm done talking about it.
- I don't get it.
- You're going.
- She's not my sister.
- She's your sister.
Our first actual conversation
was when I was 20 years old.
- Well. then that makes her your sister.
- Just drop me off at work.
- I'm not going.
- Get in the car.
I'm not going.
- Danny!
- Amy!
Alice! This is so good.
- You came.
- Hey. "Mail."
- It's "May-el."
- "May-el."
Mael. Mael.
- Mael.
Yeah. I didn't know you were coming.
I texted you.
I'm here.
I do need to talk to you about Mom.
Who?
You like the chicken?
Yeah.
So. what does he have? The flu?
Maybe.
How long have you guys been together?
It's been. like. on and off.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
I don't really see him a lot.
and we don't really talk about that stuff.
I just see him when I come into the city.
mostly for debate tournaments.
You have the most beautiful hair.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
I hate it.
I'd kill to cut it off.
But my dad. he says not to.
because he says that guys like long hair.
What guys?
I don't know.
He wants me to have a boyfriend.
You want to say hi to him?
I thought you said that he was sleeping.
He's such a baby about being sick.
Do you know what you're gonna
debate tomorrow?
In tournaments.
you don't know before.
But last time. I got a crazy one.
Do you know who Emily Dickinson is?
No.
Wait.
She did poems.
Yeah. but no one saw them
till after she died.
And she wrote in her will
that she wanted them burned
'cause she didn't want anyone to see them.
But then. her sister-in-law...
- You want some wine?
- I... I can't.
It's there if you want it.
Her sister-in-law found the poems
and published them against her wishes.
Did she do the right thing?
If she had followed
Emily Dickinson's wishes.
the poems would never have been published.
No one would ever have read them.
Is that right or wrong?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
Do it. do it. do it. do it!
Yes!
Girls night!
You gonna have a drink.
or you gonna stand there like a weirdo?
You backed down with Caleb's sister.
- Alright. what the fuck?
- You backed down.
I push. then you push. That's the rhythm.
- You didn't push.
- No. I didn't.
Because you're scared. Why?
'Cause I don't wanna lose my job.
And you know why I'm scared
of losing my job?
Because of me.
I get it. the shit with Marshall.
I'm sorry.
I didn't... I didn't ask you to back me up.
- I'm not s...
- I already knew I was leaving.
I'm not sorry for what I did for you.
Yes. you fucking are.
No. no. you told me
that he was hurting you.
and that was all I had to hear. Okay?
I never asked what he did to you.
I didn't need to know the details.
I just told him I believed you.
and now everyone fucking hates me.
These guys I've been
working with for years.
they don't fucking talk to me anymore.
Fine. fuck them.
But here's the crazy shit.
You don't fucking talk to me
anymore either.
So I lost everyone.
You know. there's a lot of people
who don't believe you about what happened.
They think I'll do whatever you ask.
no questions.
and that's exactly what I fucking did.
No questions.
You think I lied?
No.
But you don't help yourself.
You didn't even tell IA.
You just left. and he's still around.
I wanna be a lawyer.
- Like your dad?
- Yeah.
But your dad wants you
to have long. pretty hair
and a boyfriend. right?
Have you done it yet?
Like...
- sex?
- Yeah.
No. Had you ever had sex
when you were my age?
Yeah.
Lots.
Oh. my God!
Don't do that. it's hot!
You're not gonna believe it...
but I don't have any feeling
in my fingertips.
Whoa. really? Why?
I was injured when I was your age.
Oh. man. that sucks.
Yeah.
It sucked.
It sucked ass.
When did she stop taking showers?
I don't know.
When she stayed with me
after she left Marshall.
it would flare up.
She avoids the things
that remind her of him.
What are you talking about?
You didn't know?
He used to... he used to pull her
out of the shower and beat her up.
The last time...
last time. she just passed out
and he left her there
with the water running.
She never told you that?
No.
Stop. Stop holding me.
I'm fine.
- You good?
- Mm.
Alright.
I am going to barf a little.
No. I'm good. I'm all good.
No!
I'm sorry I...
I said those things tonight.
I...
I just wanted you to talk to me.
Or someone.
- You could talk to someone...
- You never asked me what happened.
Why didn't you ask me?
I just thought you'd tell me
when you were ready.
No.
You didn't want to know.
It's okay.
Look. if you're...
if you wanna take a shower...
I could just sit here.
I'm not gonna look at you or anything.
But I could just sit here
until you're done...
and. uh...
you can keep the door open if you want.
Okay.
Mira.
She's asleep. She's awesome.
Please.
I know that night. you were high.
And you were drunk.
And you don't really remember.
But there was a girl with me.
Do you remember that?
No.
You don't remember?
Don't hurt her.
You must be so scared.
You know what I used to do
when I was scared?
Look down at your feet...
and say. "Those aren't my feet."
Those aren't my feet.
Now. look at your legs and say.
"Those aren't my legs."
Those aren't my legs.
I'm not here.
I remember that you loved my hair.
You kept saying I have beautiful hair.
And when you were done...
you brought me a glass of water.
He didn't tell me how old you were.
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you for bringing me the water.
Uh. how long was I asleep?
Two days.
It's morning.
You slept like a normal person.
You want food. or...
I-I don't have any.
but you know. we could...
Look. um. Al.
I. uh...
It's Nora.
I got the CI information.
- I'm Danny Kelly. I work out of homicide.
- Danny Kelly?
Jesus. How fucking Irish are you?
I just shit a potato this morning.
How'd you get the names
of the confidential informants?
It involves a judge I used to fuck.
The man couldn't eat pussy
to save his life.
but he knew how to make gazpacho.
and he knew when to shut up.
- Was Caleb Easton on the list?
- No.
Shit.
And nothing weird
came up from his computer?
Nah. just normal porn.
And how would you describe that?
People in love having sex.
Like I said. I did the deep dive
and I got nothing.
Caleb Easton's clean.
You said his car was stolen?
Yeah.
Fuck.
Fuck. Danny. I... I can't find
anything in your notes.
Well. that depends on what
you're looking for.
His stolen vehicle report.
There was a car
parked in front of the bodega
in the security footage.
but I could only see partial plates.
Ah. that's the one.
Vehicle reports are at the bottom here.
- Why is there so much paper everywhere?
- This is... this is unbelievable.
- He wants to hold it in his hand.
- You don't have a fucking stapler.
- You know. you're making a mess here.
- A stapler?
- I had it all stacked up nicely.
- Okay. okay. Here. here. here.
He reported a vehicle stolen
February 2012.
A black Mercedes-Benz.
Look.
- What's the plate?
- I got Thomas. Charlie. Oscar.
- TCO8425?
- That's the same car.
His lawyer reported it.
Oliver Charles.
What's happening?
Dad?
I'm sorry. Mira.
He's dead.
Dad!
Mira?
Mira. Open the door.
I can't stop thinking
about that debate topic.
Emily Dickinson.
It's... so cool.
Do you remember any of her poetry?
I...
I don't really know it.
I didn't really go to school.
No. I don't remember anything.
Don't look at him. Hey. look at me.
What was your argument?
She asked in her will
that the poems should be destroyed.
And. um. wills are legal documents
that have to be...
they have to be recognized.
They were hers.
And we all took it away from her.
That feels like the right answer.
There are no right answers.
They just tell you what to argue.
Oh.
Uh. that's too bad.
Are you going to kill me?
I met your dad...
when I was your age.
And he hurt me. Mira.
He's not a good man.
What did he do?
Do you really wanna know?
Yeah.
Mr. Charles?
Hello?
Is anyone here?
I got a call from your ex-wife.
Mr. Charles?